Malta
Marist College
Malta
1789 1984
Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, New York 12601
Lowell Thomas
2.1.1.2.7
1203 Linear feet
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
Glass plate negatives; Malta
- Lowell Thomas Papers
  - Graphic Materials, 2
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass plate negatives, 2.1.1
        - Lowell Thomas, 2.1.1.2
          - Malta, 2.1.1.2.7
              - Grandmother, wearing black headdress, holding baby, circa 1918; 1 (Box 1325)
                5x7
              - Woman wearing headdress, circa 1918; 2
              - Woman wearing headdress, holding baby, circa 1918; 3
              - Woman wearing headdress, with two young boys, circa 1918; 4
              - Lace worker sitting on bench, baby in carriage at left, circa 1918; 5
              - Schneider and two women wearing headdresses, circa 1918; 6
              - Schneider and two women wearing headdresses, circa 1918; 7
              - Two officers with canes, standing on dock, circa 1918; 8
                4x5
              - Admiral Calthorpe, staff, American Consul Wilbur Keblinger and Lowell Thomas, circa 1918; 9
              - Tent hospital, circa 1918; 10
              - Street scene, circa 1918; 11
              - Mouth of Grand Harbor, circa 1918; 12
              - Girl and sheep in field, St. Paul’s Island in distance, circa 1918; 13